War. It's a dying business.
Too Late the Hero is a drama, action, war film directed by Robert Aldrich.
A WWII film set on a Pacific island.
Japanese and allied forces occupy different parts of the island.
When a group of British soldiers are sent on a mission behind
enemy lines, things don't go exactly to plan.
This film differs in that some of the 'heroes' are very reluctant, but they come good when they
are pursued by the Japanese who are determined to prevent them returning to base.
Pvt. Tosh Hearne, played by Michael Caine.
Lt. Sam Lawson, played by Cliff Robertson.
Pvt. Jock Thornton, played by Ian Bannen.
Col. Thompson, played by Harry Andrews.
Captain Hornsby, played by Denholm Elliott.
Private Campbell, played by Ronald Fraser.
Too Late the Hero is a 1970 American war film directed by Robert Aldrich and
starring Michael Caine, Cliff Robertson, Ian Bannen and Harry Andrews.
The film explores themes of world war ii, british
army, infantry, philippines, jungle.
The tone is emotional.